Aynura Mahmudova

I'm currently in my fourth years of studying Math teacher at Baku Engineering University. I am taking front-end courses for almost 3 months. In the future, want to be proficient full-stack developer. I'm greatly glad that I'll work in your team, can also be useful. It will be pleasure for me to learn other experiences.



- aynurmahmudova05@gmail.com
- Paku, Azerbaijan
- github.com/Aynur-Mahmudova5

- +994(77)7210501
- in linkedin.com/in/aynur-mahmudova-b33638227
- (instagram.com/ainoour5?igshid=YmMyMTA2M2Y=

EDUCATION

Front-End Devveloper IT Brains Academy

03/2022 - Present Baku, Azerbaijan

Math Teacher

Baku Engineering University

09/2018 - Present Baku, Azerbaijan

Foundation

Baku Engineering Universityv

09/2018 - 06/2019 Baku, Azerbaijan

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Asistant

ABB Innovation Center, ABB Tech kids

02/2022 - Present Baku, Azerbaijan

Volunteer-Math Teacher

The 238 school for elementary grade

10/2021 - Present Baku, Azerbaijan

Math Teacher

Qelebe course

09/2020 - 12/2020 Khirdalan, Azerbaijan

SKILLS

HTML,CSS,JS

Computer and Microsoft Office Skills

Teamwork

Problem solvino

Self-motivated professional

Responsible to work

CERTIFICATES

HR training (3 days) (11/2021 - 11/2021)

Nacaf Abdullayev trainings (2019 - 2020)

B2 English language (09/2018 - 06/2019)

LANGUAGES

Azerbaijan

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Enalish

Professional Working Proficiency

Turkish

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Programming

Reading

Research

Knit weave